And we are on mute.
Yeah, the recording has started.
You can unmute and start discussing. Yeah.
Yeah, Dev, I can do that.
Yeah, I saw some screens from Ankit.
He prepared one UX design for my feature
and it was very nice.
Click through and I can click the button
or something in the Figma and it is
actually explaining the story to very
clear.
So can you also do the same for this
Yes.
design?
Yes, yes,
I'll share a click-through prototype,
Sure.
yeah.
M.
Okay.
I hope my screen is visible. Yeah,
so I've updated the prompt and now say
Yes, it's visible.
let's go ahead with this.
There will be some reasoning.
And then we'll ask this question.
Yesterday what we discussed is that the
agent should have the intelligence to.
recommend one between flow service and
workflow.
That's what we're showing right now.
If we feel that no,
that is not possible for first build,
then we'll have to ask the user whether
you want to go ahead with flow service or
workflow.
I'm going ahead with the assumption that
yes,
the agent will understand and it will
recommend me.
User has to confirm that yes,
I will go ahead with the flow service or
switch to workflow.
And then I will,
the agent will be smart enough to assume
one of the projects if it has certain
intelligence.
So this is the last project or this
project has all the available connectors.
And user can just continue with that.
Or they can say, like, you know,
pick from other projects. Or, you know,
I want to see all the other projects and
I want to pick from that.
Or I want to create a new project.
Let's say user is agreeing to what the
agent is recommending.
Once again, just hold on.
Sorry for interruption.
So here also we have the assumption that
the connectors are pre-created and it is
synchronized, right?
It is all available in as it exploded,
right? And if you click create,
give an option to create a new project,
Yes.
the connectors will not be there, right?
So how are we planning to get the
connector authentication there?
So then we'll have to do it offline,
how we have had shown earlier on
Launchpad. But yeah,
but if it is predefined,
Okay.
I think that's one decision that we need
to take,
whether it'll be predefined or we give
them the option.
Yeah.
That flow is already set in workflow,
that's why I've not created it.
If we say that yes, it'll be predefined,
we'll follow this.
same process. If it is not,
then we'll have to like no,
Yeah.
they have to go to the product then.
So, if the user is creating a new project,
then you will ask that ones are not there,
so you go and create it up.
You kind of redact to the tooling.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Okay.
So, so Jyotish,
just to make it clear for everybody,
can you add a note here?
If somebody clicks the create a new
Mhm.
project action,
then it should simply follow the workflow,
M.
whatever the process we have. Put a note,
then it will clear all the questions.
Yes.
Okay.
Otherwise...
When someone sees this fresh,
then it will be again raised.
Yes.
Similarly for account selection as well.
Okay,
Yes.
we should simply follow how the account
is selected.
If more than one accounts are there,
how proposed and how a user can pick one.
So the same process should be followed
what we have followed for workflow.
Put a comment.
Yeah, yeah, done.
Alright, I'll continue. So,
user has selected a project.
Now, at this point,
I can ask some questions. These are like,
you know,
if I want more clarity on what we are
building based on the prompt,
and user can just answer them
Okay.
conversationally,
or the user can also say, like,
continue with assumptions. So, I,
this is again, like,
I think this was one recommendation that
I've heard on the demo.
We can discuss,
we can confirm that is possible.
If user doesn't have these answers,
can they just say,
continue with some assumptions and like,
you know, build my flow service?
Okay, so in this case,
user has put some answers and agent will
understand that and will create a preview.
Okay, when you expand it,
you'll see a business view.
I'll pause here.
I saw the comments on chat where I think
there was feedback that the flow,
there are multiple items.
Yeah.
I can see Biswa has put some screenshot,
even Ramu had put some screenshot.
So this is what we have in.
Yeah.
your workflow.
And there we've seen the number of steps
are usually two to three,
but in say max would be around 7.
That is why we've used this kind of an
approach and also it aligns to the
workflow technical view.
If you feel that the number of steps are
going to be more,
I think that's a discussion that we can
have. If it's going to be 60, 70,
I don't know if that is going to be the
case for a business.
view. But if that's the case,
we can consider.
I have some designs which can be
translated into a vertical view if there
are like more steps. But again,
I don't know what is the maximum number
of business view steps that a user will
see.
Yeah, Biswa,
I think you have your hand up, yeah.
Ramu is also with me,
just for your information,
Ramu joined here.
Yeah, go ahead, Biswa.
OK,
how will know that how many steps I mean,
and who will give this to number of step
details?
This will come from the agent.
The agent will give, right?
The agent can live thousands,
Yes.
so I will limit that.
Will, will, is it possible?
Possible, right? Thousand steps.
This is a programming language. Yeah,
this is a programming language, right?
So this is kind of a high level algorithm.
That's what I understand. See,
But.
let's say the user's intent is that he.
But we can it is the prompt is not
restricted only for Integration is that
like can be used for anything right?
No, this here the scope is flow agent,
right?
M.
We are assuming that the prompt is is
creating a flow agent.
Okay, so yeah,
it could be any number of step. I can't,
Okay.
I don't deny that it could be 100,
100 or 200, 300, whatever.
Okay.
It could be anything. But the idea here,
I don't know if we need to term it as a
business or something else, I don't know.
But.
The the the there is some sequence of
steps, right?
This even Bob gives some sequence of
steps saying, hey,
this is what I am planning to do, kind of,
so that is that is what my understanding
that this view will have.
If it is a planner, then this is fine.
If it is a programming step,
I don't like this because it will not fit
all the steps here, right?
That too,
I think we need to finalize what we
No.
should call it as, either it's a business,
technical, whatever,
and what it should contain.
Is it a plan or is it an algorithm or is
it a programming steps that we need to
finalize, I guess. Animesh.
English. English, correct. What?
English is it a plan?
Do we call this as a plan?
We can stick to it as a plan just like
the way Bob does that. Correct.
That's what my understanding that you see
Ohh.
we call it as a plan. You want to...
Plan whether it is a better we should
have a top to bottom so that the one more
preview you have right and so this can
you so that is the that is not not this
The second one below.
That's the technical view.
one.
Below, below, you have top to bottom,
right, vertical.
If it's a planner,
this is not top to bottom.
That one more is vertical one. Yeah,
this is if it is a planner,
Vertical, vertical.
Ohh, this looks good.
we can go with this. OK,
if it is not programming steps.
This looks better, at least to be,
and also its chat window is vertical,
right? It's like top to bottom,
so then you know it it fits better rather
than doing left to right scrolling.
Yeah, yeah.
So it is kept similar to flows workflow,
which is left to right. Again,
like I said,
because we realize that the steps are not
going to be a lot. And that's why,
and also because it aligns. I think this,
again, we had a discussion the other day,
and Tam,
you said that let's continue with a
similar design.
But if you feel that there are going to
be much more steps than horizontal.
So can you show me that vertical
rendering? I didn't see that.
When this was proposed yesterday,
I didn't see this.
No, no, no, today, today.
This is after I've read what was shared.
No, just today.
I mean, if it's a long step,
it's easier to scroll top to bottom.
Okay, I agree.
Flow normally like a multi-step process.
And yeah.
And I like this, it's very simple.
And if we can accommodate the horizontal
rendering for a complex flow services,
because flow is meant for complex
problems, right? Not like a simple.
Yeah.
Have.
Can we generate something like this?
This is business view.
Yeah, business with simple one liner,
what it is doing, one text, that's it.
Okay.
But I have to get the consent from the
engineers.
Is this something we can generate?
Yeah, yeah, I think so. I see, even Sonal,
you can you can add if you want,
or anyone who is here.
I think Prasad,
today what we are generating is the
planner, okay?
And planner looks similar to what Jyotish
Got it.
is showing. But the view,
when we talk about view,
there should be like if else or logical
constants are there.
Then how we would be redirecting, okay,
if it is a loop.
You remember yesterday we were having
discussion, if is this, else is this. So.
I feel this is just a textual
representation which can be shown at the
Correct.
right side itself instead of...
Correct, correct.
depicting it as business view.
You mean on chat?
Ha.
Yes, on charges.
No, no, whatever, like you see,
even in Rama's demo given, right,
there are these steps, one, two, three, 4,
5, 6, kind of a thing,
where it is explained.
So it is a plain English understanding of
what agent is trying to do.
So one question to you, Prasad. See,
here also it is simply represented like a
That's how I see it, yeah.
Yeah.
That's what it is.
simple flow. But my question is,
definitely we are not going to render the
Correct.
if condition loop and try catch and all,
right? That is a technical information.
If someone wanted to see that,
they can navigate to the technical view.
Alright.
But in this view,
should be simple enough to understand or
get the high level overview what this
flow service is going to do.
Correct.
Right, so...
See, there may be one step, like again,
I'm referring to the demo only. Okay,
there can be one step which might say,
see if the contract value is below 50k,
do something. Otherwise,
I'll do something else.
So that is what will be explained in one
of the steps, R2 of the two steps that's.
Correct. My question is,
can we even generate the description like
this?
Step #5.
Check if account SCV is greater than 10
million. Skip if condition if not met.
Uh-huh.
Anand.
So this is dynamically generated from the
prompt.
Correct.
Can we even identify for each step what
is the relevant description or what is
the relevant context we can have?
So can we even generate this kind of
output to render this page?
Correct, it can be done.
That's what demo is showing, right? Sonal.
Okay.
Yes, Tom, in current implementation,
it is like the step and the descriptions
both are generated using the requirements
which we are taking from the user, right,
Okay.
at the above step, like question answers.
According to that logic is important.
Okay.
Okay, so then then that that is good.
My other question is so here
Yeah.
I trade is a construct,
and it will operate on a collection of
data.
Whereas try catch is also a construct,
but that we are not going to render here.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
Huh, so here the correct, you are correct,
you are correct them the way I and.
Right,
and also if condition will not be
explicitly mentioned,
but that will go under the description,
if or else, whatever it may be.
Correct, correct, correct, correct,
correct. So even try catch, see,
Right?
Okay, okay. Now, now I got the idea. Okay.
like even try catch,
the way I remember that, see, let's say,
see, let us take the first step itself,
right? Fetch Salesforce accounts.
What if there is something goes wrong in
that?
in that step.
So Rama was giving a point below.
In case of a try,
I do something else kind of a thing.
So that might come as part of a step one
itself. So if there is an error, skip. Ah,
So as a description, kind of description.
correct, correct. See, somewhere I saw,
okay, similar to this, right?
Okay, okay.
Skip if condition is not met.
Right, similarly, the...
In case of exception, do this? Let's say,
in case of exception,
On logging.
some roll cap roll back in case of
exceptions.
Ah, roll back, I see, I logged and ignore.
Okay, then, then, then I'm good.
Like he was showing Ramu was showing.
Yeah, yeah, correct.
Then I'm good,
then I'm okay with this approach.
Instead of representing something wrong
in a horizontal fashion,
this is more explicit and it will clearly
indicate what this flow service is going
to do.
And if we have any such thing,
like a lot of YAML and what is that flow
The.
chart,
we can generate some syntax if we
generate,
then some tool can generate the flow
chart.
We can show this is the business we are
Mhm.
Okay, that is not in the scope right now.
So we'll park it for now.
doing.
Under the page, yeah.
We'll stick to what we want to achieve by
Q3 and Q4.
Hmm.
One is the business view with the simple
English, with the description,
with the numbering. That's fine.
And the technical view,
Limited.
it's a replica of what we have in the
flow.
Design Editor.
Right.
These are the two requirements.
We'll stick to this, okay?
The fishbone diagram and all those things,
maybe we'll discuss later,
all these things in the future maybe.
And.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. So see here,
sorry, one point I want to make, Jyotish.
Okay.
So.
M.
Good.
See,
Rama was asking for the second level or
third level intents.
So here I clearly see that, right?
This is step one, fetch is an intent.
The second means the second level intents,
okay.
fetch, validate, iterate,
apply a condition, or a transform. See,
these are the things. In fact,
Ramu was asking,
we should have the entire list of it so
that it becomes very easy for us.
So maybe we can discuss or create this
kind of thing internally.
Mainly for the technical folks,
maybe for Biswa or maybe Tam,
you can also add so that list of.
actions within a flow service what can
happen better we have a catalog of that.
M.
Okay,
maybe I didn't get the question clearly.
We will take it offline and discuss it.
Okay, okay, thank you.
I think moreover,
time like flow is used by technical
OK.
So...
Okay.
people, right?
So the persona is technical and we would
Mhm.
be generating the DSL code also.
And if people like technical people like
integration specialists, if they want to.
view the code and see whether everything
is good and approve and proceed ahead.
Then for those kind of persona,
how we should deal with this entire
experience. This is one more title.
So, I'm not... Thanks for the question,
Sonal,
but unfortunately I'm not in favor of
putting the persona here because...
Most of the people won't even know how
this on-prem flow services would be,
right?
But this flow pilot enabled everybody to
I.
build a flow service using the flow pilot.
And why can't we also do the same thing?
Why we need to stick to only for the
technical people, right?
So even some use cases can be better
solved using Flow Agent.
Anyone can solve it,
but only thing is it should help in an
easy way to solve the problem.
Okay, so we...
Is it fair or totally unfair?
No,
that's why we wanted your opinion into it,
like when we are building flow agent.
It was technicality.
So we will go with one persona.
So we will go with one persona,
No.
which is a technical or a developer
persona. We'll keep that in mind.
I'm not very particular about the persona
Ramu Prasad,
Uh-uh.
but my ask here is it should be
self-explanatory.
It should save time to build the flow
service. Whoever is doing, I'm fine.
Okay, okay. No, the reason is that,
you know, last one year, you know,
Yes.
half the discussion goes in persona
itself.
That's what I want to avoid and just say
that, okay, developer is the only guy.
Haha.
Yeah.
Because you remember,
I also remember that half the workflow
discussion for six months went only in
persona.
Ahh.
who is the right person who can do it and
all that.
So that that's where all the discussion
went wrong. You remember that right, Ramu?
We all know that anyone can do it.
Okay, it is getting recorded,
so I should not say anything.
That is fine. That is fine.
Whatever I said, I stick to that. So,
okay, I'm not saying anything wrong,
but that's the number one. And #2,
Yeah, yeah.
what I want is,
I don't want to stick to persona.
Okay,
but it should be self-explanatory and it
should help the person to solve the
problem.
These are the first intent I want to
focus. Instead of, okay, who will do that?
How that person will know?
I don't want to dig into that topic.
Okay.
Okay, but I like this way.
Tell me how you can generate this kind of
Mhm.
input with the detailed descriptions and
other things. Then I'm fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, selling one we have spent.
Yeah, I just wanted to add another point.
I was just,
Yeah, yeah, let's move on, let's move on.
when I was using the current launchpad
and while testing it,
I realized that there are lesser steps,
right? But whenever we,
if you're like editing and if you're
having a conversation and there are a lot
of changes, if the steps are more,
it might be difficult to really
understand what is happening.
So as a recommendation,
I feel that whenever a new flow service
view is generated,
a business view or technical view,
we should just mention that, okay, no,
two steps have been updated and just
mention that this is an updated step
where say I've said that can you increase
it from 10 million to 20 million.
So this is updated.
This is a new step that has been added.
If we can add this,
it's going to be much easier for a user
to really.
Understand what are the changes that the
agent is doing because again,
it's a technical user, right?
They need to understand what is happening
instead of just saying yes, yes,
and you know, continuing.
So this is the recommendation.
Mm.
for capturing the changes that are
happening with every edit.
K.
All right.
Now, if I uh, okay, now there's a...
What if the Iyer plan is getting updated
like?
One second.
Sorry, sorry, come again.
What if the entire plan or in the
intention is itself is getting updated,
IT.
Is it?
like not in the steps,
but as the entire business use case is
Halo, they change.
changed by the user,
then how they would be depicting it?
Mhm.
This whole thing is,
we don't have evidence,
Then it'll be completely new flow service,
right?
we don't have production,
production only name is there.
Yes.
So it will change,
it'll update it completely.
But if you're just making minute changes,
just changing a number, changing,
But they do want to enforce this that
definitely happen.
adding a new note, saying, okay,
I also want to do this,
The.
No, so it's like code base, no,
it's GitHub, everyone is like GitHub.
that change I thought it'll be nice to
capture it so user can really keep track
of the changes that are happening.
But if they change it completely,
Yeah, everyone is in Gupta.
then I think it'll just be a new version.
So.
You might really not need to show what
has changed because everything must have
Well, I think there's one political.
Yeah, yeah,
this is the idea that I didn't see it
changed.
And we can get into like the like more
detailed conversation Sonal on this.
Okay.
earlier. Yeah,
it's the velocity of the business,
I mean,
I just wanted to share that we should
but no reason to do that.
capture whatever changes have happened
because.
Yeah, yeah, instead of that,
is it chat is the better place to stand
right?
Whenever you put something there itself,
we can tell what we are changing and what
is happening.
So if you put that on chat,
it just ends up becoming very long,
the conversation.
Because right now what we are saying is
you view this business view and technical
view, you look what is changing.
And if you want to make any changes,
you put that on the chat, right?
So you're only looking at left side for
output.
Input is happening on the right side.
But if you start giving output also on
the right side,
then it might be difficult to keep track
of what is happening.
But we can explore, yeah.
No,
just just by saying add update doesn't
I, Jyotish.
make sense.
Maybe we have to do some better like it
if some way or something.
I think Biswa has already done that in on
Ohh, and what?
premise side.
One more point is, it's our artifact data,
so every time it will change anyway,
like you will get user will get a new
artifact, so if tomorrow after right.
So, so one minute,
Tam Tam will continue these 3:30 meetings
next week also.
Yep, I'm fine, but I have to drop now.
If any decision has to be taken,
Okay, yeah, yeah.
then please wait.
Should, should.
But you continue the discussion now and
because some of the people have not gone
Yeah.
through the design,
I went through the design yesterday.
If anything to be finalized,
maybe we'll close next week.
Okay, okay, Monday.
Okay, thanks.
Maybe Prasad, we can do one thing.
Let's Jyotish explore all the
possibilities,
and then maybe in the next week we can
So.
review it.
Yeah, yeah, so, so we'll do that.
Just let let Jyotish complete the one
Yeah.
till the end,
whatever is there as of today,
then we will close this call. OK,
please spend a few more minutes,
OK.
I'll take just few minutes, yeah.
So one change,
whoever has, yeah, yeah.
big change that we have is now because
after I've given my shared my project,
we are showing business and technical
view both.
Unlike the current workflow agent,
where we show a business view,
then we say configure,
and then we show technical view,
we should show it upfront.
So business and technical view should
generate upfront,
and your technical view looks very
similar to what is there on the product.
The only changes, there are a lot of,
you know,
option that you have like because we are
not giving any edit option.
It is a view only.
The only thing that you can interact is
you can click on the mapping so you will
be able to see the mapping.
You can't make any changes right now.
Later on we can make changes
conversationally,
but you'll just see the mapping.
Okay,
so what you are saying is technical views
also generated along with the business
view and then we will show both.
Yes,
that's one change from what we discussed
Right.
Okay, so the...
yesterday.
Ah, okay, so yeah,
if Sonal and technical team is okay for
it, we can do it.
That's my understanding.
Is L.L.M.
giving in the same format with business
No.
data and technical?
No, no,
LLMB is going to give in a DSL format as
I understand. This is FSL.
And DSL and business planner, right?
Ohh, sorry.
FSL, yeah, FSL, maybe.
But, Prasad.
The planner also for business,
it is a planner also will get it from LLM,
right? Both.
Correct. See,
planner in the business view,
there is a planner steps in English,
plain English, and technical, ideally,
Thanks.
Yeah, correct.
as I understand, FSL will come,
but I don't know about this view.
A passive.
Right.
It will come.
Yeah.
But once you have a facility,
it will come automatically. OK,
Yesterday.
But Prasad, yesterday, I mean,
we are making a repetitive decisions like
then we should have.
Sorry, sorry, go ahead.
Jyotish yesterday,
I think Rama has explained you right how
it works.
The plan needs an approval and once it is
approved,
then we can go to the creation of DSL and
further the flow service creation.
because it is like once user confirms the
business plan,
then only we can go ahead and present a
technical.
Otherwise it would be too back and forth
for the back end team like to generate a
DSL and then again process it for every
change.
But...
So...
Yeah.
No, Ramu was telling the other way also,
right? He was telling that, yeah,
since these are technical people,
they would like to see the code first.
He was also telling the same thing.
Yeah,
he was talking about the DSL code if user
Correct, correct.
ask on demand.
Yeah, yes.
So Sonal,
you remember yesterday's conversation in
Launchpad 3 IB?
So the same topic came up there as well,
right?
Business view and technical view need to
be generated together.
And then Ram said that, yes,
we will take a look at that.
So my intention was to just make this
experience similar.
So we can't have that in place.
like in workflow that we are showing both
together. And here we are saying, no,
Mm.
we'll have to again ask for some
validation. It.
No, but in workflow,
we are not allowing user to, you know,
I mean,
the business view of the workflow is
quite very different. And I mean,
we are doing a very different in flow
Okay.
also, right?
So maybe we can have this conversation in
the bigger platform.
With time as well,
like what would be the what would be the
best fit,
like if user approves the plan and then
we go to the technical processing,
like we go for it, right?
The DSL generation,
and then we find some errors there,
and then we allow user to fix those
errors and...
Then we finally generate,
go for generation of flow service.
Two.
So we can have the discussion because as
far as I remember,
in workflow also we had the same debate.
Like,
Very good.
and today how it is going live is with
the same approach. Once the business.
So, yeah, Sonal, I see,
I remember very initial,
like you see in January, February,
in January there were discussions where
we were discussing the opposite. OK,
where Rama has generated DSL along with
the plan. OK.
So I think both the parts are there.
We can discuss maybe once Ramu is there.
Yeah,
what you are telling sequentially that is
correct. I am not denying that. Okay,
it's a like user say yes to the plan and
then we go and generate.
It is, it is good, but yeah, if it is,
if LLM is giving both at a time, then no,
no, no, by the time we reach this view,
are we are we going to finish all the
No Prasad.
questions and we have clarity on what to
do it? Correct, correct.
That is the if we have the clarity of
what to do it, then you know what?
Yes.
This business, we are technical,
we both are same, yeah, no, yeah, yes,
questioning is a prior to prior to this,
this business, the questioning completes,
Yes.
and everything is done,
you are clear that you don't have any
pending things, right? Ideally, correct?
Are you have you have more suggestions?
Usually,
that's how you know you take use the
ChatGPT.
Probably, you know,
either it asks some questions up front
saying that, okay, it is missing.
Or it will generate that code,
then it will give you some suggestions
about how to improve and all that. Okay,
correct. So, you know,
if you take that way,
then if business view is complete,
it means the technical view is also
complete.
If you don't have any questions,
if everything is done, questions are done,
then you know you are actually ready with
the logic. Correct, correct.
Maybe after seeing the logic,
I don't know where we are going to ask
the questions about, you know,
the accounts and all that stuff.
Are we asking questions before about the
accounts itself? Accounts,
I don't know where that is coming.
It has not come in the journey so far,
right? It just said that, see,
I'm choosing a project for you where the
accounts are there.
But so assumption is that accounts are
already there. If not there,
probably that step will come,
whatever is there in the workflow.
That should be the prerequisite, right?
That should be the prerequisite. Yeah,
Yeah.
That's A prerequisite.
No, no, so sorry to interrupt, right?
Hello,
Salesforce account, yeah.
I think some of these things are already
taken care of in workflow,
and that is exactly why we are not
placing it here.
It's exactly what Jyotish was saying,
whether it's project account selection,
Ohh, got it, got it.
we don't want to repeat that,
so the journey for selecting or creating
or authorizing an account.
It stays the same as workflow.
If you feel there is some discrepancy or
Yeah.
some edge case around there, you know,
we need to of course, you know,
surface that,
but otherwise it stays the same as
workflow.
We are not going to reinvent the whole
account authorization journey again in
flow service.
I think what we really need to focus here
is, you know, this whole.
Correct.
Even if the same stands true for business
and technical view also, when, why,
how they are getting generated,
doesn't change a lot from, you know,
Then it.
the way it is for work, right? That said,
you know, in this flow service,
Good evening.
very specifically to flow service,
if you think there are any differences
from workflow perspective,
we should absolutely be talking about.
Oh, you know that piece.
Yeah. Namita,
I don't think you know that way.
I won't see much of a difference between
the flow and workflow in that aspect.
So if you have already made decisions
about, you know,
Yeah.
how to take the accounts projects and all
those prerequisite information in a
particular manner,
we can stick to the same thing for the
Yeah.
flow as well.
Yes, yes, we should. And in fact, I mean,
we'll be,
there'll be usability testing and
everything. And I mean,
Yeah.
any difference comes over there,
we would know about it. But otherwise,
yes, that stays the same as workflow.
On Namita, in workflow,
we are able to generate the technical
Yeah, OK.
view without the accounts. OK,
so that was one case, but Ramu, Ashok,
Huh, huh.
Okay.
you can confirm whether it is still
possible.
No, no, no. See, Sonal,
I don't think even in flip workflow you
can generate it, you know,
those things without having accounts.
The reason is probably we are not asking
enough questions on the workflow side
Up.
where either we are choosing the existing,
you know,
existing actions itself to do those
activities.
I don't know what we are doing on the
workflow side.
Yes, actually, Ramu, we are doing that,
but let us see if there are more accounts,
more than two or three.
We are not upsetting accounts until
unless user selects, but prior to that,
we have to show that technical view to
the user.
So that was there in the workflow,
and we had a lot of conversation like
that.
technical view must be generated once all
the data is there,
Okay.
but it was said that you generate a draft
workflow and then keep on updating or
K.
observing the information as per the user
input, like the lookup.
Okay, that's also fine. That's okay. Yeah.
So, I I think Sonal again,
the business view and technique.
Because, you know, most, you know,
most of the times.
A similar.
See,
most of the times customers want to see
the logic first,
then you know they would like to update
it. Like, that's how I also use, you know,
ChatGPT or anything.
First I see what it is doing,
then you know I will be asking more
questions or you know,
ChatGPT itself would be giving more and
more suggestions for me to ask more
questions, right?
So then it keeps on changing.
That's okay, yeah.
I think that's it. Like, Jyotish,
there should be one step saying that,
Okay, so...
okay,
validate the plan looks good to me and
you can proceed ahead.
Something like that somewhere if we can
No, here I have, here I have one question.
We are saying create this flow service,
put the set point.
Awesome.
right?
So that means is it already created in
the back end or or not?
How it is just there in the.
No, no, no. When you click on create this,
this is when it will be created.
So that's what I put in text.
There's a preview field for you to make
Okay.
Because the validation,
validation comes once, once we create,
changes if you're satisfied.
This is the validation.
isn't it? How, how,
where the validation happens before
creating or after creating,
that that's not very clear to me.
But what are we validating?
What are we validating, Prasad?
It needs to happen before itself.
This, this, whatever is generated,
the technical, the the FSL, right?
Okay.
Mhm.
Before showing here,
it would have been already validated.
So...
Ohh,
FSL is validated before it comes here,
so it, so there, so then Sonal,
there is no validation, right?
Additional validation.
No, the only thing is like,
once user confirms that, okay,
the plan looks good to us,
then we internally will validate and
let's assume if some error are there.
Then actual asset creation happens here,
actual asset is not created and deployed
right till now.
It's not.
So when you select create this flow
No, no.
Yeah.
service,
this is when it will actually get created.
Then you'll see it on the,
like if you go to the specific under
project, you'll get to see this live,
not live,
but you'll see it in the product.
till this point,
but all the validations have already
Mm.
Also,
but we need to validate it right now.
happened, like there are no errors.
That is why I'm telling you that, okay,
now you can create this flow service.
If there were certain errors, I would.
Yes.
Can we, can we,
can we validate without the mapping step?
Like, I believe flow service is,
of course, you know, this, this, this,
what we are looking at,
but mapping is an integral piece of the
flow service. I'm just asking, you know,
I think everyone here.
probably you know understands flow
service in that perspective that can we
validate without the mapping.
But.
No, mapping should have been already done.
By this time, we are showing.
So the technical view and the next step
is the mapping.
User will go and see the mapping and then
finally create this flow service.
That is review of mapping, right?
Yes.
Oh, correct, review, review, yeah.
Mapping is done, it's auto mapped,
you can make.
Mapping is done on.
Uh, automatic is already done. OK, OK,
but the user,
Yeah, you can just see it.
how is the user viewing in Jyotish
currently? Like,
they can clicking on that mapping.
So...
Yeah, you can click on this, these,
the entire block,
wherever there is a mapping available,
you can click on it and it will appear
from the bottom,
similar to the current experience.
This is a simple, like this,
just a screenshot of that.
I just remove few other things.
I think there are a lot of other
functions which...
I don't know if we can support,
we can have that discussion,
Yeah.
but I just kept it very minimal,
just a view only.
And there will show only map.
I think there are some other checkboxes.
Can you tell?
I.
I'm not sure what it does right now,
but it's just a screenshot of that.
Mm.
The good thing.
Okay, so the DSL creation, validation,
mapping happens implicitly. Okay,
and then the creation of the flow happens.
Okay.
Yes.
Once creation is done,
you can test your flow.
Okay.
You can still continue to make changes,
or you can test the flow.
She will give you this next action.
And then your test report gets generated.
And at this point, we'll ask you,
where do you want to deploy it? Like,
do you want to deploy it in your current
cloud runtime or?
you can select a different runtime.
If you say continue with this,
it gets becomes active or it gets
deployed.
So, Jyotish,
can I stick to technical view directly
instead of keep doing the business view,
then you click a tab to reach the
technical view?
But that will be a deviation right from
flow workflow. No, no, no, me as a user.
Mm.
Yeah.
I don't want to get into all this
business.
I understand what is getting generated.
Can I just say,
stick to technical as a preference?
I'm not asking for any change.
I'm just saying that, okay,
don't take me to business. Okay, show,
Okay.
okay, directly show the technical kind of.
That's all I am. I'm no,
even Rama was having the same question
yesterday.
That's a, yeah,
that that can be a that can be a feature
that we can, yeah,
maybe that can be a feature that we can
add to this.
Okay.
Like, maybe not conversationally,
maybe like, yeah, somewhere we'll have to,
Maybe like a like a click of a button or
you know something some preference.
I mean, yeah, yeah, we'll have to, yeah,
because every time a new artifact is
getting generated, right,
so it has to remember that you had made
the selection and has to then switch to
the second tab.
Yeah, yeah, so we have a preferences page,
probably we can, we can add, you know,
Okay.
some VA preferences, but...
Yeah, this is it.
Okay.
Any more questions or otherwise we'll
catch up again on Monday.
So,
so any changes that then Jyotish has to
accommodate based on today's discussion?
Only thing is confirmation, right?
Jyotish,
that that vertical view can be done or
not.
I don't know if you need to consult
anyone.
Yeah, this if we are agreeing,
so I think we should share this with Ramu.
Anand.
So I think he's back on Monday.
Sharma, yeah.
Rama is back on Monday, right? Or Tuesday?
Monday, Tuesday is back on Tuesday. No,
but mainly I'm asking from anyone.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
OK, then we, we...
This is preferred, we will go with this.
Yeah,
I think we'll have to run it through once
Oh.
Yes, we have to, yeah.
with the Launchpad design team,
that's for sure. Because yes, I mean,
in terms of scale,
just going horizontal may not be possible,
but just sort of aligning and seeing if
you know something needs to be added or.
Something.
removed. I think this one, two, no, no,
no, yeah,
This Namita, this is vertical, right?
so so far only horizontal has been done
for workflow.
This is not Harsha Gupta.
Going vertical is a new design,
to be honest, and you know,
In workflow.
Oh, okay.
we may have to we may have to dwell a
little more on, you know,
do we want to keep it like one, two,
three, 4, 5, because.
The numbers are something that is that is
part of flow service as well,
so I think some of these details have to
be chalked out.
And, yes.
Have we have we tried, like, you know,
in if how many how many steps could this
go up to?
Namita, I showed you the some,
I don't know whether you have seen the
earlier screenshots.
One customer has done 800 plus steps.
No, so those are flow service steps,
but the business steps are not going to
No, and I...
be as many as that, right? Oh,
that's what.
I know that it won't be 800.
Let's say if it is 800 and even if you
Wu.
take conservatively,
let's say for eight steps as one business
Yeah.
thing, you might still end up like,
you know, maybe 50, 60 steps. Yeah, no,
The.
Okay, okay, alright.
this challenge is there in workflow also,
Namita.
Yeah, it is coming up.
So,
there are really complex workflows which
users typically keep using, right?
They have at least forty-fifty connectors
used in their in their workflows, so yeah,
and I know also, you know,
With work, yeah.
I I still feel see.
We all use ChatGPT to everything, right?
The you know, a lot of LLMs.
I don't think you know everyone is so
used to top-down thing.
I'm not sure why we did workflow left to
right.
Probably it is because of the way
workflow is getting rendered.
But you know,
any conversation we have with any of the
AI agents, it is always top-down.
And mostly text-based. Yeah,
recently people have started adding the
UI elements into it,
but it's mostly top-down.
Okay, yeah,
so we will just run it through the
Yeah.
Okay.
launchpad team and get back on this, yeah.
Okay, great.
Anything else that we need to discuss?
Tax.
Okay, thanks a lot, Jyotish, then. Thanks,
everyone.
Thank you. Thanks, everyone.
Have a nice weekend.
Thanks, everyone. Bye.
Yeah, thank you. Bye-bye.
Ideally.